airportsindia.org.in 2012-12-07

# Privacy Policy

                                     Privacy Policy
We at Airports Authority of India (AAI) respect the privacy of everyone who visits
this site. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully so that you can understand how we
collect and use the personal information provided by you on this website
http://www.aai.aero.
By submitting your personal data to us, you will be treated as having given your
consent for disclosures referred to in this policy.
The Privacy Policy Covers...
This privacy policy covers the use of your personal information which is collected
through or in connection with this site. For the purposes of this policy, "this site"
means the official website of AAI “http://www.aai.aero” and the careers link
“http://203.145.141.162/ors used on this site.
Special Notice - if you are under 18 years old...
Please do not send us your personal information (for example, your name, address
and email address) if you are under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age
and you wish to ask a question or use this site in anyway which requires you to
submit your personal information please get your parent or guardian to do so on your
behalf.
Information Collection and Use...
We collect and use personal information (including name, address, telephone number
and email) in order to:
       •    To respond to the queries or requests submitted by you
       •    To process your requests concerning tenders, recruitments & any other
            information sought by you.
       •    For the recruitments in AAI through the process of submission of Forms
            online on this site.
To the extent required or permitted by law, we may also collect, use and disclose
personal information in connection with security related or law enforcement

investigations or in the course of cooperating with authorities or complying with legal
requirements.
We may also remove all personally identifiable information and use the rest for
historical, statistical or scientific purpose.
Collection of non-personal information...
We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of
internet browsers you use or the website from which you linked to our site. We may
also aggregate details which you have submitted to the site (for example, your age
and the town where you live). You cannot be identified from this information and it is
only used to assist us in providing an effective service on this website. We may from
time to time supply third parties with this non-personal or aggregated data for uses in
connection with this site.
Use of your personal information submitted to other websites...
We cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites
even if:
      •     You accessed the third party website using links from our website; or
      •     You linked to our website from a third party website.
We recommend that you check the privacy policy of each site you visit and contact
the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions
Submission of others' personal information...
From time to time this site may ask you to provide personal details of your family or
friends. Before providing such information, please ensure that you have obtained their
consent to their personal data being used in this way. We will not use these details in
any manner which is incompatible with this privacy policy.
Use of Cookies...
We may store some information (commonly known as a "cookie") on your computer
when you look at our site. We are able to read these cookies for information purposes
when you revisit our website. The type of information we collect as a result of a
cookie being accepted by you is specific to your PC and includes the IP address, the
date and time the PC visited the website, what parts of our website were looked at and
whether the web pages requested were delivered successfully. This information is
anonymous; it represents a computer rather than a person.

We use the cookie information to improve our knowledge of the use of our website
and to enable us to be able to ascertain whether the website is operating at an optimal
level. This allows us to enhance our web offerings to you and to provide an enjoyable
and an innovative online experience.
You can erase or block this information by changing the settings on your computer
(please refer to your help screens or manuals). If you do erase or block this
information you may not be able to utilise some features of the site
Chats, Message Boards, Newsgroups...
At this moment we don’t support Chat and other similar services on this website. If at
any time this site offers any chat rooms, message board facilities, newsgroups etc. we
may collect the information that you disclose. Such information will be used in
accordance with this privacy policy. Please note that we cannot be responsible for
other parties' use of the personal information which you make available to such third
parties through any chat room, notice board, newsgroup etc. on this site. Please be
careful about what personal information you disclose in this way.
Data Security...
We have implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your
data from unauthorised access and improper use and keep updating such measures as
and when new technology becomes available.
Change In Privacy Policy...
From time to time we may make changes to this privacy policy. If we make any
substantial changes to this privacy policy and the way in which we use your personal
data we will post these changes on this page. Please check our privacy policy on a
regular basis.
If at any time you would like to contact us about our privacy policy, you can do so by
emailing the Administrator at webadmin@aai.aero
